yiwugou.com 2019-07-01

# Purchaser Service, Yiwu Purchasing Services, Commodity Online Purchase-yiwugo.com

The Yiwu China Commodity City on the web has adopted the privacy practices with respect to personal information in operating the Yiwugo.com Website as described in this statement ("Privacy Policy"). Our products and services are offered and are made available subject to the terms and conditions set out in this statement. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**The Information We Collect**   
**Registration Information**  
At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business.

**Site Use Information**  
Similar to other commercial Web Sites, our Web Site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies". We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your registration information, publishing information or payment information so you do not have to re-enter it. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web Site and better serve our customers.

**How We May Use Information**  
We may use your collected information to service your account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our users. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web Site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at service@Yiwugo.com.

**Information Disclosure**  
In general, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your express consent, but we reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by Chinese law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary.

**Minors**  
It's not authorized to use the services of our company If you are under the age of 18. Therefore, you are not expected to provide us with any personal information. You can only use our services in the company of your parents or guardian.
